So, hi, my name's stephen wilson's
...a...measure on the media team in the operating system group
...microsoft and I'm really excited to be able to have the opportunity talk to-you today
about screen casting so today will learn how to
develop multi screen device applications using casting technologies and windows...
At the end of the session there's and evaluation so please.
Give the feedback we need it's very important to me to get the
feedback so I can continue to improve and we can...together.
So, today in...market there are a lot of devices screens and protocols author and
...users really care about is they want to be able to
...a content from a small-screen device to a bigger screen out there
and there are different standards and upper ability...can make that tricky for
developers today and our goal really windows...is my promise you
we're trying to make sharing our content intuitive reliable
and simple for both developers...for...that's my promise.
One of the things we did at the end of windows...on one is really...out what
are some consumer feedback we were getting and some of the consumer feedback was that
was really hard for users to discover...play charm that existed in windows
eight.
Another issue that uses ran into was that they couldn't actually
...device unless...previously...that device there was an issue
in discover ability additionally devices.
...only discoverable on private networks and yet to make some network changes before...you could actually
...device on public or domain networks.
A...also wanted to be able to caste more easily to other devices than just deal
...a play to devices.
We consistently got the feedback that it was really confusing to understand what
the difference was between play to in project we try to fix that
and people just said you know, play to just doesn't work reliably enough.
We agree with that from a developer perspective...developers really gave us feedback saying that
...too hard to use and every...applications.
Device selection really should be able ...application and it shouldn't be
hidden in a charm where it's hard for users to discover they really
wanted to be in charge of the full experience themselves they also
ask for the support for dip more devices
which basically means support for more protocols and they wanted to have converse api
across all platforms because windows...you could do on mobile...you could do on
the windows desktop and we really it was really confusing situation for developers.
here's what we invested in...first thing we did is we converge all api across all of our windows platforms
we really worked on improving reliability and telemetry.
Made it easier for developers to do very common task if you re easily one
...through application you made that really easy
...show that later we added wider support for common protocols out in the market so
...from...you can now use...cast you can use
blue and you can use a dial protocol comcast uses, for example.
And, one of our main goals was to imparted developer so that they can
add casting tudor application in the way they want to
add it and they can choose from the technologies they want to leverage.
So, windows ten how can...get their stuff...media from run screen to an
...there's two types of
connections their system level connections and those connections really persist throughout
your windows session so it's really like the all project that you knew you can
connect to another device using a cable or a micacious device or to a bluetooth
endpoint and as you move to applications that stays consistent and
...application-level connections so application-level connections now we're really in the hands of you
developers so you can use...minus ten api...to act casting in the way you want
in your application and that connection is really persistent for your apple only.
So, they said system level connections you can connect to
...external device.
External screens we support our cable america
asked for audio we supporter cable use be or bluetooth.
Multicast has been one of the focus points for windows ten for us ...
windows...we added mary cast pretty late in the product cycle so we really askedthe
...vendors to add a lot of that functionality
in your driver and they're really result in a different experience as you
has you had a different driver on your system as you...a different vendor so,
what we didn't understand was we took a lot of that implementation that wasn't a driver and
put in windows so that way we can make it more consistent and could really
add a lot of telemetry to figure out really what is not working with the
...we really want to figure out what is
a device that is failing for us and how can we make that better where's
...failing?
And, then we also added a bunch of os enhancements using america standard and
...direct standards so some of those enhancements
are fast ip assignments so you can connect quicker to a device that supports that we added
other enhancements like you I bc where if you connect to america
assed endpoint and that endpoint supports touch you touch that device
...touch event actually...sent back to
your sending device as if it was a local touch first pretty cool.
I want to give you some inside and what we're doing right
mary cast telemetry reliability so this is a demo slide
of the final behalf but it gives you an overview of what we do with telemetry
on itn as implementation level so each of these layers represent
...success levels and fehler levers we have or could have
and what we're doing really is that as you drill into these?
We can really figure out what are the
...we getting and what's the most important error we need to fix in order to get better.
...and we just don't look at that on a global level let's say all windows so we can really
photos funnels down to what's the exact build number what a drivers that are
being used what is the sender hardware what is the receiver hardware what is the
...version...so you can be very detailed about diagnosing issues.
And, my promise regarding to
...reliability is that now we continuously look at those reports like
...day...look at those reports and we're really trying to figure out what reduces we need to fix.
So, from...caster vices out on the market we've really been working closely together with action
...partners to make sure that we have a great experience
with popular america devices out there.
The screaming etwo...screen being pro have
beta update available that you can download today that lets you take advantage of those
windows ten enhancements that I was talking about so you can have a better user experience or you can
...keyboard to your receiver device and just start typing answer projecting or you can
...better connection etc.
So, that the slide here is that if you download the screen beam configuration utility you just
...update you can go to beta and you can get that update on your device.
So, the first-time I want to do today
...quickly demo how the system level connections are a little bit different
today than they were in the past.
For use windows key.
So, what happens right now is that all devices are being that
are recast capable are being listed here and what's the difference would windows
...one all devices that are on that I can reach are not only
devices that are...but so...click on my device?
Magic is about the happen on the other...the other and.
So, now I'm an extended...and I have my application on the other site can
movement is a studio app around if I want to or can move...
You can go to...this is pretty much what you've known in the past.
Afterwards if you want to disconnect pretty simple.
That's pretty much the inter to talk.
we're really getting to juicy part the application of a connections where developers are in charge.
So, there are three ways...developer can take advantage of the new api...windows tend to
...content the first one is called media element casting and what that is that any
...is played...local media element cannot be sent over
...receiving device and those receiving devices can be...
cast devices bluetooth devices cable or a delineated vice
so those are all the devices you can...media omen casting and as you see here there's a default cast
button...the media element that already has casting enable if you just playing video
...you get casting for free...second one is remote appointee so
remote appointees really are taking advantage of the dial protocol which is what comcast does?
And, we are we are allowing you if you have an application on your hand-held device to
launch a companion.
Application on the big-screen device and start playing the content there.
It's really a
...opportunity for users if you want to just break into that market and there are multi-view apps what
a multi-view apps multi-view apps take advantage of the projection manager api and they allow
you to basically from your local sending device create to views.
One of those...being rendered locally and the other one is being rendered on the other screen and that actually uses
...cast as a technology as well.
Some media...casting as I said anything that plays in a...video...can be
...to eater bluetooth as the only device what we did in windows
ten was aside from adding support for the protocols we did that
remove the play charm as I said...that...is
not there anymorethat also means that we had to deprecated plea to manager api that exist in windows
...that api really heavily relied on the charm.
So-if you have a windows ape on one application and you run that on windows ten
...happen is you'll never get a device selected event anymore so basically
...manager api is that.
And, then you can add use the casting api...casting back to your when the...
The nice thing is that the in a...element you get casting for free because it's just
...the new transport controls that are there one of the nice things we did is that...for projects
...we...cast into
...by just using the mediaelement casting api as so that's the way for us to reuse
...investment but is also validation at you can
do very complex things with this api in your own...so when you want to use media
...casting if you want casting at a lower-cost you want to reach a
large set of devices one api if you don't need any customization on the
receiving device because basically what is being sent over is the is the media...playing it's also important
...the capabilities of different protocols that you can use using media omen
casting and they are aware of the battery life impact when you're sending content because you're
downloading on your small-screen device and...signing it over directly.
All right so this is the first-time will be doing a...one of many.
First thing I have here is...
Student drawing correctly what I did is I created one of
screen casting sample...guessing sample is available as part of all the windows samples
...understand samples that will be distributed on...be going through
the sample once-in-a-lifetime so the first on for media
omen casting what I said was mediaelement
...so...ten that all I have to do really?
All I have to do...mediaelement to my page and then from then on I can start casting so let me show you.
As a start playing my...bunny video.
I can...cassette...
Second but.
...very simple so just by using that mediaelement I can outcast to another device out there
and they're still about their where we actually don't miss immediately close the application on the other side but
we're working on that.
So, the second.
...see...switch back.
Aside from using this very simple casting what we also did is we introduced device
...control you saw me used to select the device and, that device bigger control just really
is an easy way for you to list devices and it provide to all kinds of inline
pairing ceremonies food it's just you can specify a full to
for so you could say hey I only want to see delineated vices I only want to see america devices
only want to see dial devices...want to see all these devices together and
...picker control allows you to do that and as you click on a device you have
...that picker control will also just as I said take care of all the pairing that is needed.
So, how to use the picker control it's very simple as you simply declare one of the
flavors of the picker control you subscribe to a device selected event when
...clicks on the device and,
you can customize it so you can customize things like foreground color background color
selected color etc?
Once you've done customizing the picker you can show it then the
...shows up...user can then.
Click on a device so once users click on a
device you get the selected device back and then you can start casting so
what element casting is that as you get the casting device back you just make one
call...say request start casting...and use the casting
...from the media element so that easy to kind of replicate what...done before.
So, what I wanted to showing my next them ways?
How can I use mediaelement casting but ad my own custom my own custom
button are...a paradigm throughout the throughout the session?
So, the first thing I have here is.
Media...so for my media element I'm a little bit more fancy an added
custom...media transport controls.
And, those custom media transport controls will have my custom but if I look at those.
What you'll see is...these transport controls simply have a way to get to the custom
...button I just got my template child from my custom a template?
And, on that button I subscribe to button click different
ones that button clicked event is
actually raised by reason external event to which I'll subscribe into my page?
So, now I said hey I have a custom style well how do you get a custom style.
Because some style here is based off engineered sample style
that is available in your sdk and I just started customizing it and.
First one I have here this is a default style these are the default media transport controls and
what happens here is that there's there are a bunch of buttons in their stop up in
...rewind button volume button et cetera but...also has a caspar?
Right so this is the default cast but you...a previous demo.
But, what I did now in my own implementation in my own sample file?
I remove some of the buttons that you saw before and I
remove the default cast button and I call my custom cast button so now I can actually subscribe
...different myself and that's really what you've been seeing
...a custom cast button here so if I go back to my code.
I have my custom transport controls.
And, in my constructor here I first got the video.
And, what I do here is I get...controls my player and a subscribe to
...button clicked when...button click depend inspired?
...simply do here is...positive player.
And, I...depict once the...shown.
I got the...the by selected event.
And, as I get the casting device that was selected back.
What...here is?
I create a casting connection I subscribe to all the events and start casting.
Right here I start casting...selected device
so as you see there's a little bit more going on here than...previous demos.
What is also important to know is that when you actually use the picker what happens is the
picker control runs in a separate process so as you actually would break into the
...the picker...is actually dismissed and the selected event the
...device you get currently is actually becomes it becomes null?
The way to work around that is that as soon...before you break into a debugging
...celebrate point is to actually get a local copy of that device and
...version to the other process something working on but I do point you to
know that's something you'll have to do if you want to debug your application.
All right.
So, pretty much the same demo here.
I...default mediaelement...video playing I am a custom cast button that now
because he's black because I customized it once I selected device.
Content starts playing on my second screen again.
The next way toenable casting in your windows ten app is remote application launching and as I said
we use dial stands for discovery launch and that's really what it does discovers
your device and application and the other side and just launches it
widow worse is the following so I...really discovers all the dial enabled
...on the network which could, for example, beer xbox.
Then you get you...description back for all the receiving devices so now I know all the
device...out there and...can really start listing them inside
...device picker we ask for the application state for each of one of those
devices and then when a user clicks on a device I can launch
the application on the other side what a set of
...parameters that's really where dial gets out of the way so discovered the devices once you
pharma device then you're just launching...giving industry parameter and then you really have
to have a as a developer implement that apt outcome
...the app to app communication yourself?
So, there's a sender and receiver part through more app pointing and from a
...perspective.
Sorry.
So, from a send perspective what happens is that we converge all the api across desktop
...so we also are supporting dial one-point-six from for
working on implementingversion two-point-two as well and api
...integrated andthe device bigger control and everywhere else and in windows stand?
So, from a receiver side we've supported act dial...xbox one since obvious
twenty fourteen so in some of the major applications out there are currently already supporting
dial-in xbox.
So, when you want to use dial want to use dial if you already support dial-in
...platforms because at that point really also supporting
dial-in xbox is just a very small step for you if you want to provide
a customize experience and receiving device because you actually are running and app
on the big-screen you can just customized experience as much as you want you also
...the communication between those two app so whatever you need to implement
their your info control as a developer we also want to take device compatibility
of equation because dial actually such a small protocol
so well-understood the different devices really behave really well with...you don't have any of those issues?
As using dialing you're sending media crossword most of the time you send across as a reference to the media
...cloud.
So, what you actually get on...on the sending devices great battery life because once you're actually
...content that devices really you
...the reference and accomplice are streaming let's say you're xbox and any
of any of work on the on the sending devices done?
Next step is ...showing you how easy it is to add the...windows...
So, you use...you can use a dial picker flavor.
And, what you simply do there is iq specify filter and you say hey my dial application amos,
for example,
consoles of video and what I'll do is that once somebody brings up that picker
we'll make sure debbie only show...devices out there that have
...video installed?
Once a devices selected called...device
...that method and...equivalent...disconnect.
When somebody clicks...transport controls the picker shown?
Many user...device.
...outcast...doing that as we grab the dial
device.
...updating picker saying hey we're connecting we're getting a local copy.
Of the selected device on the so we're calling get dial
...video.
And, never really launching.
So, we see at the recast launches
...string the string is an example but it's a pretty good example of what you,
for example, can do for casting media we have a...code that allows the to
...the cloud we have a reference to the content your currently playing so that you can easily
pulled down before you actually have done the rendezvous and then we have time offset?
Where you basically the position where you were...once?
...six...can set...picker status to connected and all...itself.
Disconnect
us very similar when the user clicks on this connect you get that you get
dial device that you want to disconnect from back and then on you-can call stop
piecing depending on how to dial server implements stop...the application
could just be staff or it could completely be terminated downloaded from memory if you
dole one that type of behavior you could just user app
to app communication and just lowly stop local playback if you want to?
Onestop you think is completed I'm updating...status and say ham disconnect that
...hiding...bigger so that was how you quickly add dial on the client.
This is how you add dial on.
The xbox one using the windows...implementation of xbox one.
So, in my manifest what I'm simply saying is that hey this
...it supports style and...video is my
...protocol name very simple so what happens now as soon as application is installed and
somebody queries for dial device that has come to...video
...app installed the xbox one is being return is one of the results.
When the application is...so many...
device jan activated event in your application...called?
And, what we did is as part of the arguments were telling you
...being act activated for as a dial
...dial device?
So, if you being activated as a dial devised pretty...time at that point to start just
...parsing the arguments so these are restraining arguments that we discussed earlier
before I'm getting the video id I'm getting my position and I'm getting my
...code from then on I'm playing the video.
So, let's let me show you how that works in action.
So, I have my xbox one on one side
...look at the time and time clocked in start.
What's happening here is that I have my xbox one.
And, at my local application.
I have the code here for the dial sender
and the receiver so as a dial on the dial
sender side I again I just have my media element.
With my custom transport controls emait custom...
That...here when.
A user has actually selected device I'm going to start casting so what
I've shown you before is...this is a little bit more complicated little bit more complicated version of the code
...into that but, what happens is that I'm calling
the picker and you see this is like rap and really nice try catch blog?
...way to do the reason for that is that if I break into debug are as I said before the
picker actually doesn't exist anymore in is being dismissed so right now from
...picket outside the display status will fail that's...that's...
What happens...code is that based on the dial device idea and getting back getting my dial device?
And, then I'm getting my dial-up instance based
...the name so if the dial application exists.
What I'm doing here is that I am launching my application on
the other device once that is being launched?
Really this is where.
All of the app to app communication needs to be instantiated
...need to run for yourself that's what happens on the sender side.
On the receiver side what happens.
You have the on activated event that's being...
You have the on activated advantages be called.
So, as I said and jan activated event I'm just
checking the activation arguments and find my activation kind to be
dial receiver if it is dial receiver what I will do eventually is
...to my receiver page?
...the receiver page.
I will parse out the dial arguments...you've seen before.
And, start playing the video basically I'm just roughly launching
gap with the video I got past and, the app gap communications really part of this demo right now.
Semi video playing locally now when I click on my device bigger
...filtering down to all dial devices intimacy my xbox...your site?
Now if you look at the other side.
All...that's...
And, you see the app is now playing
Boom agrees that.
Pretty great.
So, the other part what's nice about this application is that and
...everybody kind of internalize that this app is really running.
Locally and it is running on the xbox.
So, that's really degree part of that the way to quickly.
Where you actually debugging deploying un the xbox?
Is simply by?
Once you have an xbox one that runs windows ten as a remote machine you type
india p address of your xbox.
And, then you can just deploy to your...so that's pretty,
pretty...pretty cool I'm going-to try and deployed to the xbox to might be
...remote debugging service that might have stopped and then we'll just have to start again.
Right so that it's not.
So, what I'm doing now is...connecting to my xbox?
And, then so, this is hopefully something you would never have to do yourself.
So, now the debugged should have been restarted my xbox and if I now deployment application what
...before should work now.
So, you see I'm just running the app now locally on my xbox it's loading yap a
loaded to a default page that shows you
a video still video of the casting part.
So, that's really how easy will be to develop xbox one apps
...my your windows universe lab that I can
have be a sender on the client-side...I deployed to
...sudden answer receiver...pretty great?
Again, it's pretty cool right.
So, the last way to...casting to your app are the multi-view applications.
...back so multi-view applications as I said as you can generate to different
screens.
From one device.
And, then project that second screen on america device...connect cable device so what we
didn't understand was we really converse those api across desktop and
...platforms those existed more or less on desktop before
...now are completely functional mobile as well.
We integrated them with the windows stand api and device picker control you've seen before.
And, one of the big changes that was made from windows equal one is that you can
now selected divisor casting to packet in windows eight-point one
...the first instantiate america connection and then you could connected
...device around those two screens now you can really just
pick that from within your api as so when you want to use multi-view applications.
Multi-view applications you really can customize what is being played on a second screen so as I said that's
a second view your rendering and you can run that I've us customers you want to.
And, if you want you by doing so you really take advantage of the as prunes we've
made...and windows ten.
How do you addsupport for multi-view apps?
Again, it's pretty simple once user clicks on the casting
button...you do is you instantiate your picker control you
added device class saying this is my projection device once devices
selected the picker device elected method is called and I'm showing my picture.
If you've ever implement a multi-view apps...this is a very
reduced version of what you have really have to do to instantiate those two views but once you have
...views instantiated you just call projection manager start projecting
...synch capacity to
...views you've created and the selected device id to which you want to start project.
So, what I did here is that?
I created.
I multi-view application multi-view application locally again just as my
media element with my custom casting button and what I do is as I'm as I'm
casting as...generating my second view I am
...projection view page and that page aside from just having a
mediaelement on there it actually hasanother set of transport controls?
Where you can pretty much put on anything you want what I did want to do is ...
difference so when I first was using media element casting what happened on the second screen device
can really positive content there because there weren't any pas...controls or transport controls
there so I want to add those and I'm adding these by using the multi-view...
So, these controls are invariant of
the transport controls you've seen before what I did do is I added a stop rejecting.
Button to those, for example, and, will be using...
So, I have my application buffering the video here.
Filtering down to.
Recast devices in my neighborhood are monitors.
Pixel second launching the second
wvu on the other screen and as that happens you'll see actually just my...what it
does it start buffering the content and...playing the content on this other screen.
Additionally I have my custom media transport controls I added there so,
I can going-to full-screen if I want to you know,
I can stop rejecting I can switch diffuse if whatever I need as a user
...cool I'm pretty excited about this one especially since
as a developer you can really star choosing which of
these technologies works well for you which of these...want to take advantage of.
That's my biggest point of the day is that as we've
discussed these different levels of casting you can really start...so.
You can combine mediaelement casting remote appointee and multi-view...in your
in your code to make sure that you really create the best possible experience for the
...user selects what that means is that if they selected
...device you want to use dial if they select america device might be really good to create
an experience that has takes advantage of the multi-view app system to generate that
second screen in a custom way but if it doesn't support any of those what you could
do is stand take advantage of the media element casting api as and just simply...the video
on the other side so what I've done right now is that I'm targeting recast devices
I'm targeting dial devices on targeting gianni and bluetooth devices
out on the market and for a user that is one experience...one
cast button and one way to connect to it mone list of devices after choose out of
...get the
...experience that is the best possible experience on the device.
The way you do that in your application is by adding.
The device bigger.
Control...you add the device bigger you start adding folders so the first filter
...adding is...show me all-america
...devices the second one is show me all devices that can render video so those
...my ideal any devices and the last filter is show me all the
devices that support dial and have...also video app installed?
When a user has selected advice...pick a device selected methods?
So, the picker to the user right now so that's why I'm doing here the second screen here
...really clicked on a device so what I'm trying to
figure out in a simple version is a first try to see if...the device that
a selected does that device like support dial.
If it supports style I want use dials so I'm starting my dial casting right here.
I'm getting...dial-up and I'm calling request launches...
Secondly if my divisive not support dial all check to see if it
supports the projection manager api as using...cast.
If it supports, supports those...start projecting that custom you seen before.
...my device does not support dial it does not support america assed because of
my filter and...either support deal and...are bluetooth at this point and,
I can target those using the casting api so that's kind of my last resort here I'm using
the casting api...and,
I'm calling request...on the casting source that was playing in the media element and I'm hiding my picture.
So, that's really great way that you can add all of these together.
So, in...sample here as you download it.
The first thing that you'll see is out right now if you download the sample today there's two things after
warning about first...the api is don't work in their kern build of windows you'll get but,
also be fixed secondly you'll see
there's some small work-arounds right now and as we resolve our
bugsy out keep updating the samples so as you download the sample with the corresponding...have
...decode become cleaner,
cleaner but I really don't want to hide anything from you so, what you'll see today is?
Is that what...through what I'm doing here is I'm
subscribing to my player events second of the status and getting a video
for my data provider I'm...a source locally and then I'm subscribing to
...custom transport controls?
And,...picker now and then of subscribing to already
events my picker offers so device
...disconnect and dismissed so when
...users connected to a...disconnect button will show up when they click on the disconnect
...disconnect different will get fired if they bring up the picker and they don't selected by
cyclic next to it the dismissed eventful get fired.
And, then...folders and that's really where to...shows them right now.
For dial there's a custom...filter I specified here normally you would just be able to
call ...defies dot get the by selector
...currently incorrect and, the same goes for on casting device
get the by selector they all don't play well together when you're combining
all these technologies and lastly there's a projection manager filter you...
So,...many user.
Some picker device selected get the idea of my device.
I have device information...device information object is to general representation
...a generic device that is being selected and what I'm doing here is
at first I'm really trying to use dial failed on use my
...to measure api if that does not work
...use mediaelement casting and as you go into all these methods...really like
what really revisiting what you...all the individual technologies there?
So, if I run the sample.
What's nice about this at this point is that.
If I start playing content here I can really select
...like my xbox or memory cast device stochastic content
to so from users' perspective and windows I'm coming back
...promise I made you is that you can now.
You can all target the widest set of devices out
on the market with different api supported them windows
...we create one user experience so that's pretty great so as a summary.
Windows ten where allowing developers...broader set of devices
in the market using a broader set of protocols as a developer you really are
impart to agcas into your application added in a way you want you can use a device
picker control you can choose not to use the device
bigger control you canmix and match all the different kasich
...sari before ideally my...action is that as you
are working on this please try to combine them...experience in all devices out there in the market.
I want to thank you for your time today I have time for questions and then please take some
time to evaluate the session as well
...the feedback is very valuable to me...thank you for today.
Question actually there regarding chrome
...airplane javanese so we supports croquet so,
...question was do we support our chrome caster airplane we curly
support comcast as a device because they use dial as a technology are still.
So, as you implement...
on windows as a sender you'll be able to target you'll be able to target the xbox one
...comcast advice fire tvs and other devices out on the marketers really pretty brought.
For comcast I think they should still
...the...on the crocus ij in order to support the question is
...you implement the receive...comcast side.
Yes, and, no, because what you can do is that on
...actually is a default type of application that exist there and you could target
...default application if you want to you even using.
what about close...closed captioning handling on the on the on this website
do we need to do anything for closed-captioned are depends...which type of ...which type of device really,
yeah, okay, so, if you need to incremental truncation on the
streams so...hundred from sander...or is it
again the device specific so what happens with authentication on a stream is that?
It depends on the technology but let me go into the into detail on that a little bit more
...you do element casting...casting source.
What we really filtered the list down to
is any of the devices that support the content protection you're using?
...so that's what the mediaelement casting and,
then withdial you really are in control yourself it really is the app
...to determine whether the content is a lot of the play or not and
it is very similar if you use the projection manager api...because what you're really doing is that your
...video locally so, yes, you have to do...with the production manager api
is but it shouldn't be a lot of work...should be able to easily...that yourself.
Hi, the dial stuff can I use that
just appear to apps together on two different machines or is it only for video so,
the question is a dial-up only for video or can I just...to
...applications on different devices it really is not restricted to media ...it is?
What oftentimes is the case the dial service that is running
...most of time only implemented on a media receiver types of devices like xbox like chrome
...tvs and such?
The second question is can windows ten act as a
...receiver someone use my surface three...as a
...it curly does not will.
Maybe okay moi.
Any other questions I can help it.
There is not a default app right now I'm sorry.
Yeah, there is not a default app on xbox one now but we have that
I something we really want to start working on now but, we were really focused on getting all the plumbing to work and,
the demos moi.
But, yeah, it should be really easy to add that for us as well.
All...I think that windows...going to support the top
...using...she.
The...the if the
...to...can ingestion only the system...connection what application
...that...the tapped as really focused on the system level connections right now.
Any other questions I can help it.
Right
I want to thank you for your time enjoy the movie tonight enjoy the rest of...conference thank you for coming.